[Music]
on behalf of the philippine cancer
society
i would like to sincerely thank fwd live
philippines
for supporting our advocacy and
awareness programs
for cancer low health literacy
and the high cost of treating cancer are
major factors
in the prevention and treatment of the
disease in our country
it doesn't also help but now we have
covered 19
added to the challenge of treating our
patients
the donations of fwd life philippines
however
allow us to continue our programs in
research and awareness and of course
through our focus patient services we
would like to thank
fwd live philippines for helping our
kawabayans
fight the big c mabuhay
fwd live philippines
[Music]